

MUHAMMED ATIF ATIYA

CONTACT

- 0 102 0704 029
- muhamedattif@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/muhammedatif
- Toukh, Qalyubia

Military status

Exempted

COURSES / TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Django Framework
- React JS (Concepts)
- Rest APIs with Django
- JAVA SE (OOP)
- PHP (Intermediate)
- MySQL Database
- **PostgreSQL**
- SQL
- HTML/HTML5
- CSS3/Bootstrap
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Ajax
- **SEO**
- **ERP Next**

PROFILE

A Junior Software Engineer, I am a self-motivated person who is willing to go above and beyond on any project. I'm interested in the Web development field, I have an intermediate background in Back-End and Front-End Web Development, APIs, Ajax, and Databases. Not only Web Development, but I also would like to get into and gain experience in AI, Data Science fields.

EDUCATION

Faculty of Computers and Artificial Intelligence Helwan 2016 - 2020 University

Bachelor's degree of Computer Science & Software Engineering. GPA: 3.47

CERTIFICATES / INTERNSHIPS

Artificial Intelligence Analyst - Explorer Award and Mastery Award

IBM Training

Certificate of Excellence 2018

Award from Software Engineering Program – Helwan University

2020 **InnovEgypt Certificate**

InnovEgypt Training

EXPERIENCE

Vision Student Activity 2020

IT Member

Graduation Project

Automated CRM for restaurants (Application that answers Customer's calls and help them order their food) (AI).

2018 - 2021 Freelance projects

Hotel Reservation System (PHP)– Airline Reservation System Blog/Customer Support System - ChatApp-Friend system (Django)

Python Developer at Variiance

2021 - Present

2020

2019

Writing and testing code, debugging programs and integrating applications with third-party web services

LINKEDIN ACCOUNT



GITHUB ACCOUNT



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Computer skills
- Photography
- Voice Over

LANGUAGE

- Arabic
- English